<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Restouran  </string>
    <string name="b_hamzanwadi">HAMZANWADI UNIVERSITY</string>
    <string name="b_fakultas_teknik">Faculty of Engineering</string>
    <string name="b_teknik_informatika">Technical Information</string>
    <string name="b_diyawan">Diyawan</string>
    <string name="m_coktail">Coktails</string>
    <string name="m_indinesian_food">Indinesian Food</string>
    <string name="m_mocktail">Mocktails</string>
    <string name="m_westren_food">Westren Food</string>
    <string name="m_timur_tengah_food">Middle Eastern eats</string>
    <string name="d_daftar_menu">MENU LIST</string>
    <string name="name_dark">Dark and Stormy</string>
    <string name="bahan_dark">Material\n . 2 ounces. dark rum\n • 3 ounces. ginger beer\n • 1/2 ounce. lime juice (optional)</string>
    <string name="des_dark">Directions \n Fill a tall glass with ice cubes. Add the rum, then pour in the ginger beer and lime juice. Stir with a bar spoon. Garnish with lime wedges.</string>
    <string name="name_French_75">French 75</string>
    <string name="bahan_French_75">Ingredients \n • 2 ounces. London dry gin\n • 1 tsp. powdered sugar\n • 1/2 ounce. lemon juice\n • 5 ounces. rough champagne</string>
    <string name="des_French_75">Directions \n Beat gin, sugar and lemon juice well with crushed ice in a cold cocktail shaker. Strain into a Collins glass half full of cracked ice. Cover with champagne.</string>
    <string name="name_Boulevardier">Boulevardier</string>
    <string name="bahan_Boulevardier">Directions \n Beat gin, sugar and lemon juice well with crushed ice in a cold cocktail shaker. Strain into a Collins glass half full of cracked ice. Cover with champagne.  Ingredients \\n • 1 1/2 ounces. bourbon or rye whiskey\\n • 3/4 ounce. Campari\\n • 3/4 ounce. sweet vermouth</string>
    <string name="des_Boulevardier">"Instructions \n Stir ingredients with ice in a mixing glass until cool. Strain into a coupe glass. Garnish with an orange twist. "</string>
    <string name="name_body_mary">Bloody Mary</string>
    <string name="bahan_body_mary">"Ingredients \n Mixture\n • 1/2 c. tomato juice\n • 1/4 inch radish, chopped\n • 1 tsp. Worcestershire sauce\n • pinch of celery seeds\n • 4 hot sauces (Tabasco, Tapatio, etc.)\\n • 1/2 lemon juice, fresh squeezed\\n • 1/2 lime juice, fresh squeezed\\n • pinch of salt sea\\n • a pinch of black pepper\\n • 1 tbsp. vodka\\n • 2 ounces. vodka\\n • 6-8 ounces. Bloody Mary mix "</string>
    <string name="des_body_mary">"Directions \n Blend tomato, radish, Worcestershire, and celery juices until smooth. Add hot sauce, lemon juice, lime juice, salt, and pepper, then puree. Adjust the mixture depending on how spicy, salty, or citrus you like it. Add 1 tbsp. vodka to stabilize the mixture and keep the juice fresh, then puree. Mix 6-8 ounces. mix with 2 oz. vodka into a glass with ice. Pour back and forth into another glass 3 or 4 times to mix, then garnish however you like. "</string>
    <string name="name_gimlate">Gimlet</string>
    <string name="bahan__gimlate">"ngredients \n • 2 ounces. London dry gin\n • 2/3 ounce. Rose lime juice "</string>
    <string name="cm__gimlate">"Directions \n Beat ingredients in a cocktail shaker with crushed ice. Strain into a chilled cocktail glass, and garnish with lime. "</string>
    <string name="name_moscow_mule">Moscow Mule</string>
    <string name="bh_gimlate">"Ingredients\n • 2 ounces. vodka\n • 4-6 ounces. ginger beer\n • 1/2 ounce. lime juice\n "</string>
    <string name="cm_moscow_mule">"Directions\n Squeeze the lime juice into the Moscow Mule mug, then add the used shell. Add 2-3 ice cubes and vodka, then fill with ginger beer. "</string>
    <string name="nm_Aperol_Spritz">Aperol Spritz</string>
    <string name="bh_Aperol_Spritz">"Ingredients \n • 2 ounces. Aperol\n • 3 ounces. prosecco\n • 2 ounces. (or extra) club soda\n • orange slice "</string>
    <string name="cm_Aperol_Spritz">"Directions\n Make Aperol, prosecco and club soda in a wine glass over ice. Garnish with fresh orange slices in a glass. "</string>
    <string name="nm_mojito">Mojito</string>
    <string name="bh_mojito">"Ingredients \n • 2 ounces. white rum\n • 1/2 ounce. lime juice (freshly squeezed)\n • 1 tsp. powdered sugar\n • 3 mint leaves\n • club soda or seltzer "</string>
    <string name="cm_mojito">"Directions \n In a small Collins glass, mix the lime juice with 1/2 to 1 tsp. very fine powdered sugar. Add mint leaves, puree on the sides of the glass, then fill 2/3 cup with crushed ice and pour over the rum. Add the squeezed lime rind and cover with club soda or seltzer. "</string>
    <string name="nm_Margarita">Margarita</string>
    <string name="bh_Margarita">"Ingredients\n • 2 ounces. silver tequila\\n • 1 oz. Cointreau\n • 1 oz. lime juice\n • coarse salt for the edges "</string>
    <string name="cm_Margarita">"Directions\n Rub the rim of a chilled cocktail glass with lime juice and dip in coarse salt. Whisk the tequila, Cointreau, lime juice, and ice in a mixing glass, then strain into a salted glass over ice. "</string>
    <string name="nm_Whiskey_Sour">Whiskey Sour</string>
    <string name="bh_Whiskey_Sour">"Ingredients \n • 2 ounces. bourbon or rye\n • 2/3 ounce. lemon juice\n • 1 tsp. powdered sugar\n • 1/2 egg white "</string>
    <string name="cm_Whiskey_Sour">"Directions\n Beat ingredients well with crushed ice, strain into a chilled cocktail glass, and garnish with lemon wedges and/or maraschino cherries. "</string>
    <string name="nm_bulebery_mojito">BLUEBERY MOJITO</string>
    <string name="bg_bulebery_mojito">"Ingredients: \n 6 mint leaves\n cup blueberries\n cup lime juice\n cup simple syrup\n 1 cup sparkling water\n Ice cubes to taste\n How to make: "</string>
    <string name="cm_bulebery_mojito">"How to make\n Put blueberries and mint leaves in a shaker, mash coarsely.\n Add lime juice, simple syrup, and ice cubes. Shake briefly.\n Pour into a glass.\n Add sparkling water and ice cubes. Garnish with mint leaves. "</string>
    <string name="nm_nice_pear">NICE PEAR</string>
    <string name="bh_nice_pear">"Ingredients\n 250 ml of pear juice\n 60 ml of lemon juice\n 2 tbsp sugar\n Soda water to taste\n Ice cubes to taste\n "</string>
    <string name="cm__nice_pear">"How to make\n Mix all ingredients in a shaker.\n Pour into a glass and give enough sparkling water.\n Garnish with pear slices on top. "</string>
    <string name="nm_pinepple_corbbler">PINEPPLE COBBLER</string>
    <string name="bh_pinepple_corbbler">"Ingredients:\n 60 ml of strawberry juice\n 30 ml of lemon juice\n 100 ml of pineapple juice\n Soda water to taste\n Ice cubes to taste "</string>
    <string name="cm__pinepple_corbbler">"How to make\n Put pineapple juice, strawberry juice and lemon juice in a shaker filled with ice. Shake briefly.\n Pour into a glass. Add ice cubes and sparkling water.\n Garnish with pineapple and lemon wedges. "</string>
    <string name="cm_holidy_sherly">HOLIDY SHIRLEY</string>
    <string name="bh_holidy_sherly">"Ingredients:\n cup orange juice\n cup sprite\n 2 tsp simple syrup\n Cherries for garnish\n Ice cubes to taste "</string>
    <string name="cm__holidy_sherly">How to make: \n Pour orange juice, simple syrup, and sprite into a glass. Stir.\n Add ice cubes to taste. Stir again.\n Garnish mocktail with cherries. Serve.</string>
    <string name="nm_Virgin_Watermelon_Margarita">Virgin Watermelon Margarita</string>
    <string name="bh_Virgin_Watermelon_Margarita">"Ingredients:\n 1 medium watermelon, sliced\n cup lime juice\n 4 tbsp pineapple juice\n 1/3 cup sparkling water\n Ice cubes to taste "</string>
    <string name="cm_Virgin_Watermelon_Margarita">"How to make:\n Puree the watermelon in a blender.\n Add the lime juice and pineapple juice. Blend again.\n Pour into a pitcher that has been given ice cubes.\n Add sparkling water on top. Give a slice of lime. Serve. "</string>
    <string name="nm_Rendang">Rendang</string>
    <string name="bh_Rendang">"Ingredients \n Saute ground spices until fragrant, add meat, stir until it changes color.\n Add turmeric leaves, lemon grass, and kandis acid. Stir gently.\n Add water. Cook until the water reduces. Stir per "</string><string name="cm_Rendang">"How To Make \n Saute the spices until fragrant, add the meat, stir until it changes color.\n Add the turmeric leaves, lemon grass, and kandis acid. Stir gently.\n Add water. Cook until the water reduces. Stir gently every now and then.\n Add coconut milk, cook over medium heat.\n Leave until meat is tender, gravy is dry, and oily. Lift, serve. "</string>
    <string name="nm_Rawon">Rawon</string>
    <string name="bh_Rawon">"Ingredients: \n 500 grams of beef slightly fatty\n 2 liters of water\n 3 lemongrass stalks, crushed\n 3 cm galangal, crushed\n 5 lime leaves\n 2 bay leaves\n 4 tbsp oil for frying\n 2 spring onions, chopped\n Fine seasoning:\n \n 5 shallots\n 3 cloves of garlic\n 2 candlenuts\n 1 tsp coriander\n 2 cm ginger\n 2 cm turmeric\n 3 pcs red chili (optional)\n 4 pcs old keluwak, steamed, take the contents\n 2 tsp salt\n Complementary:\n \n Shrimp crackers\n 100 grams of short bean sprouts\n 4 salted eggs\n Sambal\n "</string>
    <string name="cm_Rawon">"How to Make \n Cook the meat over low heat\n Add the bay leaf, lemon grass, galangal, and lime leaves until the meat is tender and cooked.\n Remove the meat, then cut into small pieces.\n Strain the boiled beef, set aside with the sliced ​​meat. .\n Puree all the ground spices, stir-fry until fragrant.\n Remove and add to the meat broth.\n Cook over low heat until it boils again.\n Taste, if the taste is right.\n Add the chopped green onions. cut, simmer briefly. Rawon into a bowl, sprinkle short bean sprouts on top.\n Serve with warm rice, salted egg and chili sauce. "</string>
    <string name="nm_Sate">Sate</string>
    <string name="bh_Sate">Ingredients: \n 250 g of chicken fillet, cut into cubes, then stabbed into a skewer\n 1 sliced ​​lime\n 100 ml of cooking oil\n 3 shallots, thinly sliced\\n 5 tbsp sweet soy sauce\n rice white or can be replaced with rice cake to taste\n Peanut seasoning:\n \n 3 pieces of garlic\n 4 pieces of red onion\n 100 g peanuts, fried\n 2 grains of candlenut\n salt to taste\n 150 ml of chicken broth\n 2 tbsp cooking oil\n Sambal:\n \n 15 small red chilies\n 4 cloves garlic\n salt to taste\n cooking oil to taste</string>
    <string name="cm_Sate">"How to make:\n To make peanut sauce, puree garlic, shallots, peanuts, salt, and candlenut. Saute the peanut sauce until it smells good, then add the broth and then cook until thickened and then remove. Set aside.\n Next, mix 2 tablespoons of peanut sauce with added 2 tablespoons of sweet soy sauce, then dip the satay, then grill until half cooked. Remove and then roll again in the seasoning, continue to burn again until cooked, remove.\n For the onion sauce, saute the garlic until half cooked then remove. Next mix the garlic plus a small red chili, and salt, puree. "</string>
    <string name="nm_Tahu_Bacam">Know Bacam</string>
    <string name="bh_Tahu_Bacam">"Ingredients:\n 400 grams of tempeh/tofu, cut according to taste\n 800 ml of coconut water\n 100 grams of brown sugar, comb\n 2 tablespoons of sweet soy sauce\n 1 bay leaf\n 1 cm galangal, crushed\n tsp salt\n oil for frying\n Puree :\n \n 6 shallots\n 4 cloves of garlic\n tbsp coriander\n 3 lemongrass sticks, take the white "</string>
    <string name="cm_Tahu_Bacam">" How to cook: \n Unkep or boil tempeh with coconut water, brown sugar, sweet soy sauce, bay leaf, galangal, salt, and ground spices until cooked and absorbed. Let cool.\n Heat oil, fry over medium heat until brown. Remove, drain and serve. "</string>
    <string name="nm_Soto_Ayam">chicken Soto</string>
    <string name="bh_Soto_Ayam">"Ingredients: \n 1/2 chicken\n 2 liters of water\n 250 gr long bean sprouts, remove the roots\n 1 leek, finely sliced\n 1 1/2 tsp salt\n 1 tsp sugar\n 3 pieces lime leaves\n 1 stalk of lemongrass, crushed\n 2 segments of galangal, crushed\n 2 segments of ginger, crushed\n Fine seasoning:\n \n 1 tsp round pepper\n 8 shallots\n 4 cloves of garlic\n 3 turmeric segment \n Complementary :\n \n 2 celery sticks finely sliced\n 1 tomato, sliced \n fried onion\n lime, sliced "</string>
    <string name="cm__Soto_Ayam">"How to make :\n Boil the chicken until the chicken is tender. Reduce the heat.\n Saute ground spices, lime leaves, lemon grass, galangal, and ginger until the aroma comes out. Remove and add to the chicken stew. Stir well and cook until it boils.\n Add salt, sugar, powdered stock, scallions, and bean sprouts. Stir well and cook for a while then remove.\n Serve in a bowl and add additional ingredients. "</string>
    <string name="nm_sop_Buntut">"OXTAIL SOUP "</string>
    <string name="bh_sop_Buntut">"Ingredients: \n 1 kg oxtail\n 2 cm ginger, crushed\n 1 stalk of green onion, sliced\n 1 tbsp, cooking oil\\n 200 gr carrots, cut into slices or dice\n 250 g potatoes, diced\n Nutmeg powder to taste\n Water to boil to taste\\n Fine seasoning:\n \n 6 red onions\n 3 garlic\n 1 tsp round pepper\n Complementary:\n \n fried shallots\n tomatoes, chopped dice\n scallion coarsely chopped "</string>
    <string name="cm_sop_Buntut">"How to make Put the oxtail in a saucepan until it is submerged in water, boil over the fire until it boils. Remove the foam that floats on top and the first cooking water of the oxtail.  This is useful so that the broth does not smell.  Heat the cooking oil, then stir-fry the ground spices.  Next, add the nutmeg powder, ginger, scallions until fragrant.  Next, add the oxtail and add water.  Boil in a closed saucepan over low heat.  Boil carrots and potatoes in a separate pan until cooked, then drain.  After the tail is soft, take the tail and then strain the broth, then put the tail back into the filtered broth.  Bring the oxtails back to a boil over low heat.  Place the carrots and potatoes in a bowl then pour the broth and oxtails, then add the toppings. "</string>
    <string name="nm_Mie_Goreng">"FRIED NOODLES "</string>
    <string name="bh_Mie_Goreng">Ingredients\n 1 packet of egg noodles as needed as prawns\n 5 fish balls\n 2 carrots\n 1 leek\n 4 cloves of onion garlic cloves To taste enough cooking oil\n 3 teaspoons of sesame oil (optional)\n 1 1/2 teaspoons pepper powder, soy sauce, salt, water/chicken stock</string>
    <string name="cm_Mie_Goreng">"How to make:\n Boil egg noodles until soft but not too mushy, remove and drain.\n Slice carrots, meatballs, and spring onions.\n Prepare the peeled prawns.\n Puree the onion and garlic.\n Sauté the ground spices until fragrant, add the shrimp, meatballs, carrots.\n Add the sesame oil then add the water, salt, pepper and a little sweet soy sauce and finally add the noodles and spring onions and stir until absorbed.\n Taste, add salt to taste. Pour into a plate, Serve "</string>
    <string name="nm_Ayam_Goreng">FRIED CHICKEN</string>
    <string name="bh_Ayam_Goreng">Ingredients:\n 1 young free-range chicken, divide into 4 parts 1 lime, squeeze the water 300 ml of young coconut water 2 bay leaves Cooking oil to taste Fine seasoning: 5 cloves of garlic 5 grains of candlenut 2 cm of galangal 2 cm of salt turmeric How to make :</string>
    <string name="cm_Ayam_Goreng">How to make Chicken Rub with lime juice. Add ground spices.\n Mix well, let stand 30 minutes.\n Boil chicken in coconut water, add bay leaf.\n Cook over low heat and stir until the chicken is tender, and the gravy thickens.\n Heat a lot of oil, fry the chicken until golden brown.\n Lift and drain. Serve fried chicken and chili sauce, complemented by fresh vegetables.</string>
    <string name="nm_Ayam_Panggang">RED ROCK CHICKEN</string>
    <string name="bh_Ayam_Panggang">Ingredients: 1 domestic chicken, cut into 10 parts One teaspoon of lime juice 1 teaspoon of salt 3 tablespoons of oil for frying 2 bay leaves 2 cm of galangal, mashed 600 ml of coconut milk from 1 grated coconut 1/2 tablespoon of salt 1 tablespoons brown sugar 1/4 teaspoon ground pepper Fine seasoning: 8 red onions 4 cloves of garlic 4 large red chilies, roasted 8 curly red chilies, roasted 4 candlenuts, roasted</string>
    <string name="cm__Ayam_Panggang">How to make chicken marinade with lime juice and salt.\n Bake until half cooked.\n Set aside.\n Heat oil, saute ground spices, bay leaf, and galangal until fragrant.\n Add coconut milk, salt, brown sugar and ground pepper.\n Stir well. Cook until boiling. Add chicken, reduce heat.\n Cook until the spices are absorbed and all the ingredients are cooked. Lift.\n Grilled chicken while smeared with remaining spices until fragrant and browned.\n Lift. Serve.</string>
    <string name="nm_Nasi_Goreng">FRIED RICE</string>
    <string name="bh_Nasi_Goreng">Ingredients 1 plate of white rice 2 sausages, sweet soy sauce, salt and soy sauce 2 tablespoons mixed vegetables 1 tablespoon butter fried shallots 1 clove of garlic 1 egg broth powder (optional) Complementary: Cucumber Crackers, sliced</string>
    <string name="cm_Nasi_Goreng">How to make:\n Crush the garlic then chop and cut the sausage.\n Beat the eggs.\n Heat the butter until it melts then add the eggs, garlic and sausage, stir fry for a while then add white rice.\n tablespoons of powdered broth Taste a little, if the taste is not enough, you can add a little more salt.\n If it feels right, pour the rice into a plate and add fried onions.\n Serve while warm.</string>
    <string name="nm_Samosa">Samosa</string>
    <string name="bh_Samosa">Ingredients for samosa skin: n 250 g wheat flour \n 50 g tapioca flour\n 1 tsp salt\n 2 tbsp margarine enough water\n Ingredients for samosa filling:\n 250 g ground beef\n 1 diced carrot \n 1 diced potato\n 3 garlic cloves\n 3 garlic cloves 1 tsp ground black pepper\n 1/2 tsp ground nutmeg \n 2 cloves\n 1/2 tsp cardamom powder 1 cm ginger 2 cm galangal 1 tsp salt 1 tsp oyster sauce \n 1/2 tsp chili powder</string>
    <string name="cm_Samosa">How to make the filling for samosas: \n Saute the carrots and potatoes that have been cut into squares until tender.\n Add the onion, garlic and ground beef. Sprinkle ground black pepper, nutmeg powder, cardamom powder, chili powder and salt.\n Crush the ginger and galangal. Include it with the stir-fried meat. \n Add the oyster sauce and turn off the heat when it is fully cooked.\n How to make the skin and cook the samosas: Put the flour, tapioca flour, butter and salt in a bowl. \n Knead until smooth and set aside for 30 minutes. Prepare a milling tool, dust it with flour or oil so it doesn\'t stick. Thinly grind and cut into triangles. Shape the samosa skin that has been cut into triangles with a cone shape. Fill the samosa skin with the provided filling. When finished, seal the bottom side in a three-leg shape. Fry on low heat. Remove the samosas when they are cooked and crispy. Kriuk!</string>
    <string name="nm_Chea_Tea">Chai Tea</string>
    <string name="bh__Chea_Tea">Ingredients needed:\n 1/2 tsp ground cinnamon\n 1 dew/flower grass\n 1/2 tsp ground ginger\n 2 green cardamom\n Pinch of nutmeg powder\n 1 tea bag\n 2 tbsp sweetened condensed milk\n 1 cup hot water tea</string>
    <string name="cm_Chea_Tea">How to make\n Green cardamom crackers, put in a tea cup.\n Add cinnamon powder, deaf, ginger powder, nutmeg.\n Put sweetened condensed milk and pour hot water into a cup\n teabag, then remove when it turns color it\'s a bit brown</string>
    <string name="nm_Roti_Khubz">BREAD KHUBZ</string>
    <string name="bh_Roti_Khubz">Ingredients needed:\n 250 gr wheat flour\n 2 tablespoons white powdered milk\n 1 tsp sugar\n 5 g instant yeast\n 1 tbsp oil\n 1 tsp salt\n Water to taste</string>
    <string name="cm_Roti_Khubz">How to make\n Put a cup of water along with sugar and instant yeast in a bowl . Make sure the yeast is active, indicated by the presence of small bubbles.\n Add the flour, milk powder and oil. Knead until smooth.\n Let dough rise for 30 minutes.\n After rising, sprinkle salt and knead again.\n Sprinkle flour on a rolling pin so that the dough doesn\'t stick, roll it into a flat ball. You can measure the thickness at will.\n Light the stove with a candle flame. Prepare the Teflon without giving anything.\n When the Teflon is hot, place the dough. Flip over until desired doneness.</string>
    <string name="nm_Kofta">KOFTA</string>
    <string name="bh_Kofta">Ingredients needed: \n 250 g ground beef\\n 3 tbsp bread flour\n 1 egg\n 1 clove of onion\n 2 leeks\n 1/2 tsp ground nutmeg\n 1/2 tsp black pepper powder\n Pinch of ground cinnamon\n 1 tsp salt\n 1/2 tsp dried basil\n 1 tsp chili powder\n Mozzarella cheese slices to taste</string>
    <string name="cm_Kofta">How to make\n Cut the onion into small cubes. Sauté until fragrant and wilted.n Thinly slice the leek.\n Mix the ground beef, scallion, egg, onion and breadcrumbs in a bowl.n Sprinkle nutmeg powder, ground black pepper, cinnamon powder, chili powder and salt. Stir until evenly distributed.\n Make a dough of ground beef with a round shape. Don\'t forget to put the mozzarella cheese in the middle.\n Fry the kofta over low heat. Remove when brown.</string>
    <string name="nm_Nasi_Kebuli">RICE KEBULI</string>
    <string name="bh_Nasi_Kebuli">Ingredients:\n 250 grams of fluffier rice\n 1/2 free-range chickenn Oxtail\n 2 cardamom sticks\n 1 lemongrass stick\n 1 tsp fine nutmeg or powder\n 3 cloves\\n 3 tbsp butter \n 8 cloves of shallot\n 5 cloves of garlic\n 1 tsp round pepper\n 1 tsp cumin\n 1 tbsp coriander\n Fresh ginger approx. 1cm\n 1/2 tbsp salt\n Fried onions (complementary) \n Pickles (complementary)\n Crackers or chips (complementary)</string>
    <string name="cm_Nasi_Kebuli">How to make:\ Puree the onion, garlic, round pepper, cumin, coriander, ginger, cardamom, lemon grass, fine nutmeg, cloves. Salt chicken. stir until everything is smooth.\n Wash the fluffier rice according to your choice.\n Cook the rice using chicken stock that has been mixed with ground spices.\n Pour the oil in a frying pan, add the oxtail.Fry until cooked using medium heat.\n Pour rice in a molded bowl, place on a dinner plate.\n Drain the fried oxtail, place it on the same plate as the rice.\n Add fried onions, crackers or chips, and pickles if you like</string>
    <string name="nm_Nasi_Buyani">BRIYANI RICE</string>
    <string name="bh_Nasi_Buyani">Materials needed:\n 200 g of clean and diced mutton\n 30 g of walnuts\n 65 g of chopped dates\n 3 green chilies, sliced \n 400 ml of yogurt\n 450 ml of fresh milk\n 1 teaspoon lime juice\n A little oil for frying\n 500 gr Rice that has been soaked and washed clean\n \n Seasoning mashed:\n \n 1/2 teaspoon Cumin\n 6 Shallots\n 1 tsp. Ginger powder\n 1/2 tsp. Cloves\n 3 Cloves of Garlic\ Salt to taste</string>
    <string name="cm_Nasi_Buyani">How to cook Goat Briyani Rice:\n Heat a little oil in a frying pan then put all the ground spices into it. Wait until you smell the fragrant aroma while stirring.\n Put the soaked rice into the stir-fried spices.\n Also add the chopped mutton -cut. Stir until evenly distributed, then pour in the milk and add the chopped dates, and walnuts.\n Keep stirring the ingredients like liwet rice until they are completely cooked.\n Enter the sliced green chilies and lime juice while stirring slightly and cover the top for a while just\n Remove the cooked briyani rice. Serve</string>
    <string name="nm_Lemon_heard">Lemon herd</string>
    <string name="bh_Lemon_heard">Ingredients\n - 2 Potatoes the size of your choice\n - 2 Tbsp salted butter, melted\n - 3 cloves of garlic, chopped\\n - 2 Tbsp lemon juice\nc- 3 Tbsp honey\n - Pinch of salt\ n - 1 Tbsp parsley\n - 1/2 tsp black pepper</string>
    <string name="cm_Lemon_heard">\n How to make- Preheat the oven to 175 degrees Celsius\n - Prepare a heat-resistant baking sheet or container, line it with aluminum foil\n - Wash the potatoes, don\'t peel the skin\n - Cut the potatoes thin, but don\'t break them\n - Mix stir all ingredients together until smooth\n - Spread on potatoes, making sure each piece is exposed to the spice rub\n - Bake at 175 degrees Celsius for 30 minutes\n - Spread the seasoning again, then bake for another 30 minutes\n - Serve</string>
    <string name="nm_Sopo_Tahu">Sopo know</string>
    <string name="bh_Sopo_Tahu">Ingredients:\n - 2 pieces of tegg tofu, cut into pieces with a little cornstarch and then fried\n - 5 pieces of young corn, sliced oblique\n - 1 carrot stick, thinly sliced \n - Prepare 100 gr of meat/seafood ( can be changed according to taste)\n - 5 Fish balls, sliced\n - 1 stalk of leek, sliced \n - 3 cloves of garlic\n - 1 Tbsp oyster sauce\n - 2 Tbsp soy sauce\n - 1/2 Tbsp fish sauce\n - 1 Tbsp sweet soy sauce\n - A little sugar\n - To taste salt and pepper\n - Water to taste\n - 1 Tbsp sesame oil\n - 1 Tbsp cornstarch, dissolve with a little water</string>
    <string name="cm_Sopo_Tahu">How to cook:\n - Saute garlic in oil until fragrant, then add meat/seafood until it changes color\n - Add fish balls, carrots, young corn\n - Add oyster sauce, soy sauce, fish sauce, sweet soy sauce, water , sugar, salt and pepper\n - Cook until boiling and taste, add sesame oil, scallion, then dissolve with cornstarch solution</string>
    <string name="nm_French_toast">French toast</string>
    <string name="bh_French_toast">Ingredients\n - Egg 1pc\n - Vanilla\n - Sugar 1 tbsp\n - Plain liquid milk</string>
    <string name="cm_French_toast">How to make:\n - Beat eggs, vanilla, sugar and liquid milk\n - Dip the bread in the dough\n - Bake in melted margarine\n - Cook until brown\n - Serve with ice cream</string>
    <string name="nm_Chisken_Cordeb_Blue">Chicken cordon bleu</string>
    <string name="bh_Chisken_Cordeb_Blue">Ingredients:\n - 1 Chicken breast\n - Smoked meat\n - Slice of mozzarella, can be replaced with kraft quick melt\n - 1 egg\n - To taste salt\n - To taste pepper\n - To taste flour multipurpose seasoning\n - Enough potato flakes, can be replaced with breadcrumbs</string>
    <string name="cm_Chisken_Cordeb_Blue">How to cook:\n - Cut the chicken breast in half, then thinly slice the chicken breast, cut in half but don\'t break it\n - Flatten with a meat mallet, if you don\'t have one you can use a pestle, beating gently so the meat doesn\'t crumble\n - Sprinkle with salt and pepper to taste evenly\n - Put the bacon on top of the chicken breast, then the cheese then roll up. Pin a toothpick so that the roll doesn\'t open\n - Coat with all-purpose flour evenly\n - Dip into the beaten egg evenly, then coat with potato flakes or breadcrumbs evenly\n - Store the chicken in the refrigerator at least 1 hour\n - Fry the chicken using a deep frying technique or with lots of oil, make sure the oil is hot and using a low heat, fry until golden brown\n - Chicken cordon bleu is ready to be served with fried potatoes, vegetables and brown sauce</string>
    <string name="nm_Garden_veggie_chickpea_sandwich">Garden veggie chickpea sandwich.</string>
    <string name="bh_Garden_veggie_chickpea_sandwich">Ingredients:\n - Prepare 15 ounces of canned chickpeas\n - 3 scallions, finely chopped\n - 2 celery stalks, finely chopped\n - 1/4 Carrot, grated\n - 1/4 Chopped bell pepper\ n - 1/4 Chopped Pickles\n - 1/4 Cup low fat mayonnaise (you can use vegan mayonnaise)\n - 1-2 teaspoons mustard\n - 1/8 dry Dill (optional)\n - 1/8 Spoon salt tea\n - 1/8 Teaspoon black pepper\n - 3 tablespoons sunflower seeds without salt\n - 2 tablespoons chopped basil\n Sandwich ingredients:\n - Wheat bread\n - Lettuce\n - Leaf basil (optional)\n - Tomatoes (optional)\n - Onions (optional)\n - Spread for sandwiches (can be spicy mustard mayonnaise, and tomato sauce)</string>
    <string name="cm_Garden_veggie_chickpea_sandwich">How to cook:\n - Place the chickpeas in a large bowl, then mash using a potato smasher or using a food processor\n - Pour the scallions, grated carrots, celery, pickles, and black pepper into a bowl. Stir until smooth\n - Add mayonnaise, mustard, dill, salt, sunflower seeds and pepper\n - Arrange slices of whole wheat bread, place basil and lettuce as desired\\n - Pour over sandwich filling to taste, and cover again with sheet bread</string>
    <string name="nm_Rosemary_chicken_with_sauteed_vegetables">Rosemary chicken with sauteed vegetables</string>
    <string name="bh_Rosemary_chicken_with_sauteed_vegetables">Ingredientsn - Chicken thigh/breast fillet\n - Corn flakes\n - 1 Carrot stick cut into match\\n - Salt\n - Pepper\n - Pepper grains\n - Rosemary\n - Thyme</string>
    <string name="cm_Rosemary_chicken_with_sauteed_vegetables">How to cook:\n - Season the chicken with salt, ground pepper, rosemary and thyme\n - Heat the grill/teflon with butter then grill the chicken until cooked\n - Heat a frying pan with a little butter then fry the corn and carrots, add a little water and season then cook until cooked\n - Serve</string>
    <string name="nm_Spicy_tuna_roll">Spicy tuna roll</string>
    <string name="bh_Spicy_tuna_roll">Ingredients\n - Prepare 5 ounces of minced tuna\n - 1 tablespoon sriracha sauce (hot Thai sauce)\n - 1/2 teaspoon chili oil\n - 1/2 teaspoon rice vinegar\n - 2 tablespoons eat chopped spring onions\n - 1.5 Tablespoons low fat mayonnaise\n - 6 Sheets of nori\n - 1.5 Cups of Japanese rice</string>
    <string name="cm_Spicy_tuna_roll">How to make:\n - Mix the tuna, sriracha sauce, chili oil, rice vinegar, chopped scallions, and mayonnaise\n - Prepare a tatami or sushi roller, place the nori sheets on top of the tatami. Add the rice over the seaweed and spread it up to 1/4 of the nori. Try not to make it too thick\n - Place the tuna in the middle of the rice\n - Roll it gently, and put a little water on the end of the nori sheet to stick it\n - Cut the sushi roll into several pieces\n - Serve on a plate with soy sauce or wasabi</string>
    <string name="nm_Chickpea_salad_with_lemon">Chickpea salad with lemon, tuna, and olives.</string>
    <string name="bh_Chickpea_salad_with_lemon">Ingredients\n - Prepare 15 ounces of chickpeas\n - 1 Can of tuna\n - 1/2 Cup Kalamata olives, coarsely chopped\n - 1/3 Cup coarsely chopped onions\n - 1/4 Cilantro, chopped coarse\n - 1/2 teaspoon salt\n - 1 tablespoon lemon juice\n - 2 tablespoons olive oil\n - Black pepper to taste</string>
    <string name="cm_Chickpea_salad_with_lemon">How-to\n - Mix all ingredients in a large bowl\n - Serve with toasted French bread</string>
    <string name="nm_Sun_dried_tomato_basil_pasta">Sun dried tomato basil pasta</string>
    <string name="bh_Sun_dried_tomato_basil_pasta">Ingredients\n - 1 Box of pasta or spaghetti (variant can be adjusted)\n - 1/4 Chopped sun dried tomatoes (Italian tomatoes that have been sun-dried and soaked in oil)\n - 1/2 tablespoon chopped garlic \n - 1 tablespoon balsamic vinegar\n - 1/2 cup basil, coarsely chopped\n - 1/2 medium onion, finely chopped\n - 1/3 cup olive oil\n - 3 tablespoons milk unsalted almonds\n - 1/4 teaspoon salt\n - 1/8 teaspoon pepper</string>
    <string name="cm_Sun_dried_tomato_basil_pasta">How to cook:\n - Boil the spaghetti until cooked, drain\n - Put all ingredients in a blender until it becomes a paste\n- Prepare a saucepan and heat the olive oil\n - Sauté the onions until fragrant\n - Add the previously cooked pasta made, add basil leaves, chopped dried tomatoes, and also spaghetti\n - Stir until smooth, and serve on a plate</string>
    <string name="nm_Spanish_chickpea_and_spinach_stew">Spanish chickpea and spinach stew</string>
    <string name="bh_Spanish_chickpea_and_spinach_stew">Ingredients:\n - 2 tablespoons or 30 ml of olive oil\n - 3 cloves of garlic, finely chopped\\n - 3 cloves of red onion, finely chopped\n - 1/2 medium size onion\n - Cumin powder to taste\n - 1.5 teaspoons paprika powder\n - 1/2 Chili powder\n - 1/2 teaspoon salt\n - 2-3 teaspoons brown sugar\n - Black pepper to taste\n - 2 x 400 grams of canned tomatoes (or you can make your own tomato paste)\n - 1.5 Cups of boiled chickpeas\n - 200 grams of spinach\n - Almonds to taste\n - Brown rice (can be replaced with white rice to taste)</string>
    <string name="cm_Spanish_chickpea_and_spinach_stew">How to cook:\n - Heat the oil in a non-heating pan, then sauté the onions until fragrant. Add the garlic and continue to saute until brown\n - Add the cumin powder, paprika powder, chili powder and salt. Sauté until smooth\n - Pour in the canned tomatoes and cook on low heat until thickened\n - Sprinkle with ground black pepper, stir briefly, then add the chickpeas\n - Put the spinach leaves in the saucepan, then cover the pan for 3 minutes. Stir briefly then turn off the heat\n - Serve with rice</string>
    <string name="coktail_list">Coktails List</string>
    <string name="masaIndo_list">Indonesian Food List</string>
    <string name="minummok_list">Mocktails List</string>
    <string name="masBarat_list">Weastrean Food List</string>
    <string name="masTimTum_list">Middle Eastern eats List</string>
    <string name="coktail">Coktails</string>
    <string name="masakan_indonesia">Indonesian Food</string>
    <string name="mocktail">Mocktails</string>
    <string name="masakan_barat">Weastrean Food</string>
    <string name="masakan_timur_tengah">Middle Eastern eats</string>
</resources>
